

# **PROFILE**

7 months of experience in front-end development knowledge in HTML, CSS, React Js, Redux. I have done different projects in university and made Livestock, Student QR Code websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript. Now working on more projects. 6 months of experience in android apps development, knowledge in XML, Java, Kotlin. I have made 2 apps, Fake Call Prank and Best Match.

# CONTACT

PHONE: 0304-5127214

WEBSITE:

https://alijaffiery.github.io/portfolio.git hub.io/

FMAII

Shanz5127214@gmail.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Reading Books Travelling Cricket

# ALI SHAN HAIDER JAFFIERY

Software Engineer

# **EDUCATION**

IQRA University, H-9 Islamabad Campus

2022

BS (Software Engineering)

Islamabad Model College For Boys, F-10/4 Islamabad

2016 ICS

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### AppTrick [Android Developer]

October, 2022 - Present

Perform daily tasks

# Lion Forces Academy [Notes Maker]

January, 2021 - Present

- Making notes for academy
- Upload objectives on website

### Self-Employed [Front-end Developer]

March, 2022 - Present

- Student QR Code
- Livestock

# Hazza Institute And Technology [Android Developer]

March, 2022 – September, 2022

- Fake Call Prank
- Best Match

# National Consulting for Business & Management Solution (Pvt) Ltd. (NCBMS) [Data Entry Operator]

January, 2019 - March, 2019

- Data Entry of Loans forms.
- Supervision of submitted forms.

# National Testing Service (NTS) [Data Entry Operator]

February, 2017 - April, 2017

- Data Entry of Government employment forms.
- Verification of filled forms.

### **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React Js, Redux, VS Code
- XML, Java, Kotlin, Android Studio